Center for International Education and Global Strategy; Records ua550
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Files, 1967-1978; 7.53 cubic ft.
  - Brockport Caen, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Brockport Copenhagen, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Brockport Manchester, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Buffalo U. General, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Buffalo U. Greenhole, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Buffalo U. San Juan, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Cortland Neuchatel, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Oswego Caribbean, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Oswego St. Malo, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Empire State College General, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Geneseo Consortium General, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - New Paltz General, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Urbino General, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Urbino Grad INS696, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Oneonta General, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Oneonta Israel, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Oswego General, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Oswego International Broadcasting, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Oswego Pisa, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Oswego Puerto Rico Exchange, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Plattsburgh Montreal, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Potsdam General, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Binghamton, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Brockport, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Buffalo, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Manchester, England Didsbury of Education, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - SUNY Buffalo, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Cortland, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cortland Neuchatel, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Milne Yucatan Program, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Fredonia, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Geneseo, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - New Paltz Ibadan, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - New Paltz, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Oneonta, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Oneonta Israel, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Oswego, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Plattsburgh, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Potsdam, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Potsdam Madrid, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Nee Forms, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Paris, Jean, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Rom. Language Chairman Selection Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Students Comments, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Moscow Info, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Grenoble Evaluations, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Ludko, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Alex Corr Fischer Nice, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - SUNY Wide International Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Postes D'Assistant, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - All Program Directors, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Africa, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Africa Senegal, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Pendings Italy Urbino, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - program Director, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Albany Transnational Forum, Undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Manchester program Summer, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Cyprus, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Albany Minority Group Studies Institute Frankfurt, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Santiago, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Summer Program for Freshmen at GOETHE Institute, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Maron, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Richard Rice, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - English as a Second language, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ISWA Program Information Sheets, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Centre Socis, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Course Plan for "Development of the American Economy Proposed for Inst of American Studies, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CIDOC Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ALL DIES, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - EOP, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Financial Aids Whitlock, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - SUNYA Inter-Dept Registrar, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - SUNY Inter Dept FSA, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Budget Proposals + Materials SUNYA OIP, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ADM Manual for Overseas Academic Programs, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Registration SUNY Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Rome, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Community Relations, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Self Survey of Nebraska, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Summer Correspondence WMD-Office SUNYA, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Directors - Letters of Appointment, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Site Descriptions, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Site Descriptions, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1970-19791 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Site Descriptions, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - New Paltz - Plans for Collaboration, 1968-19790 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Evaluations, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Germany Student Evaluations, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Forms Acceptance SLAP, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Mindanao, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Dean of International Studies Correspondence and Memoranda [ 1 of 3 ], 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Dean of International Studies Correspondence and Memoranda [ 2 of 3 ], 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Dean of International Studies Correspondence and Memoranda [ 3 of 3 ], 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Moscow Evaluations Fall, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Budgets, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1974-19975; 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Journal Items, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - ISIS, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Haiti, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Auclair Jean, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - South Asian Students, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Strasbourg, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - SUNY Wide Proposals, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Dantas, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Sanouillet Michel, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973; 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Site Visitations, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - US Dependent Schools European Proposal Consortium, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - State Education Department, 1968-1973 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - International Visitors, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Foreign Language Education M.A Program, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Peace Research in America, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - International Activities, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Program Abroad General, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Silliman University, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CWC Correspondence, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Slocum John, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Social Welfare Project, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Report of Active and Pending Cooperative Arrangements SUNY Programs, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Copans Sim, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Council on International Educational Exchange, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Inter-Institutional Activities, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Derrick William M, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Inter-Institutional Programs, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Transnational Professorships, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Robbins, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Teaching Abroad, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Lockett, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Paul Miwa, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Singapore Pasti, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Professor Slametmuljana, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Woo, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Singapore, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence Slocum John, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Singapore Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Publicity Nanyang, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Xavier A. Fernandez Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Russia Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Singapore Financial Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Hak Chong Lee, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Nice Program Memoranda, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Singapore Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Singapore Information Prepared by Professor Egelston, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Pre Session Hawaii, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Lawrence Huang, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Channing Liem, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Ronald Knapp, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Nanyangm Program Planning, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Student Evaluation Goethe Institute, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - SLAP, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Forms, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Planning Committee Albany - Oneonta, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Exchange Professor, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Copans Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Allen Caswell Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Peter Macris Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Maron, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Richardson Rice, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Richardson Rice Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Richardson Rice Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Rasamimanana Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Exchange Students Wurzburg, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Program, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Course Frequency List, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Nice Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Proposer Reorganization Nice Program, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Charles Coleman Correspondence, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Simon John, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Exchange Students, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Singapore General News Releases to Parents, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Forms for Nanyang Program, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence Egelston, Martha, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Journal Items, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Registration Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Travel International, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - SUNY Travel Abroad, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - List of Students in OIP, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - International Studies and World Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Overseas Credits General, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - International Program Misc, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - materials for meetings, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Indonesian Project, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Greece, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Education - Study Abroad in Advanced Classroom Teaching TESL + Bilingual Education, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Council on International Educational Exchange, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Conseiller Cultural Ambasador de France, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Comparative Education, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Association for Cultural Exchange, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - JF Kennedy University, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - International Visitors, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Ireland Exchange Program, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Japan, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - ISWA Independent Overseas Study, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Middle East, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Program Information Sheets, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Program Proposals, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - SUNYA International Program Budgets, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Blackburn Hewitt Proposal, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - British Theatre, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Pre-Freshman Summer language Program, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Program in Internship in Puerto Rico, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - International Student Office, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Rome, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - AID Service in African Countries, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Brussels, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - College of Arts SUNYA, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Exchange Visitors Program, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Honduras, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - International Education Act, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Non-Western Committee of Capital District College Meeting Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - University of San Marcos, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gut'l Program -Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Swana - Southwest, Asian, North African Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - International Studies, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Overseas Program Policy Statement, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - International Studies and World Affairs, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - AuClair, Jean Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - International Studies and World Affairs, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - International Education Budget, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Institute for American Universities, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Princeton Cooperative Program for Critical Language, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Transnational Forum, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Wolters - Travel Planning, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Transportation Klinger, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Alan Patureau, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Special Washington Report, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Robinson, Liliane, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Sectionlist Summer, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - International Studies and World Affairs, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Committee on the Future of International Studies (COFIS). Files [1 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Committee on the Future of International Studies (COFIS). Files [2 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Technical University of Berlin - Albany, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Foundation Juliana, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Prof. Grunsky, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - University of Strasbourg Student Exchange, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Mrs. Haide Russell German Consulate Correspondence, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Oyster Bay International Center Files [1 of 2], 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Oyster Bay International Center Files [2 of 2], 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - International Faculty & Student Exchange - Information Bulletins, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - SUNYA International Programs, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - SUNYA International Programs, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Immigration Procedures for Foreign Faculty, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Canadian Studies Institute, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Dar es Salaam, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Education and World Affairs Correspondence, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - International Programs SUNYA, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cuernavaca Correspondence, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Education in England/Scandinavia, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Conference of Directors of International Education, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dr. John Slocum's Folder form Conference of Directors of International Education, 1966; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Reports From March International Studies and World Affairs Conference, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Conference of Directors of International Programs Packet, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - International Reporter Service, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - SUNY Directors of International Education Correspondence and Reports [1 of 2], 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - SUNY Directors of International Education Correspondence and Reports [2 of 2], 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Hungarian Theatre, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Guadalajara Program Administrative Files, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Inter-American Languages and Area Studies Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - International Programs Office Forms, 1973-1985; Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - International Programs: China, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - International Programs: France, 1973-1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - International Programs: Germany, 1967-1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - International Programs: Israel, 1973-1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - International Programs: Italy, Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - International Programs: Mexico, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Netherlands Program Brochure, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - International Programs: Russia, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - International Programs: Singapore, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - International Programs: Spain, 1971-1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Spain Booklet SUNY Brochure, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - D.I.E Meeting, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Independent Study Guide - General, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Independent Overseas Study General, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Theatre in Great Britain, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - British Theatre, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Wurzburg Interim Program at SUNYA, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Oswego - General, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Brockport - General, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Buffalo - General, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Cortland - General, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Other SUNY Program Lists, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Other SUNY Program Lists, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Brockport - General, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Print Shop, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Course Descriptions Other SUNY Program, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Other SUNY Program Lists, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Brockport - General, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Letter File Key A-Z, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Officer Letter File #750-1057, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Officer Letter File #501-749, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Policy for Overseas Academic Programs, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Overseas Program Planning Procedures, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Office Letter File #220-546, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Office Letter File #1-219, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Special Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - International Programs Committees, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Committee on International Study Meeting Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SUNY Albany - Germany Materials, 1967-1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Student Materials and Brochures, 1971-1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SUNY Albany - Moscow State University Promotional Materials, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Inter-University Correspondence, 1974-1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Courses with International Content, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Moscow State University Exchange Program Information Packet, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - SUNY Planting Field Conference Report, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Office Letter Files and Program Binders, 1970-1979; 1.66 cubic ft.
  This series is primarily made up of letter files from the Director of International Programs from the time period covered, Charles Colman. This series also contains a number of binders documenting the administration of study abroad programs and are organized by year. These binders include information provided to students applying for these programs, orientation materials, travel iteneraries, as well as contact information of students, faculty and support staff overseas affiliated with the program.
  - Cyprus and Israel Program Orientation Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Wurzburg Program Informational Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nice Program Files, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nice Program Information Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Madrid Program Informational Letters, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Madrid Program Informational Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Spain Summer Program Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - France Summer Program Files, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Germany Summer Program Files, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Germany Summer Program Files, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Nanyang Exchange Program, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - World Cultures + The Human Condition 1, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - World Culture + The Human Condition 2, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - World Culture + The Human Condition 3, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - World Culture + The Human Condition 4, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - World Culture + The Human Condition 5, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - World Culture + The Human Condition 6, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Summer Program Informational Binder, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Year-long Programs Binder [1 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Year-long Programs Binder [2 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Year-long Programs Binder [1 of 2], 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Year-long Programs Binder [2 of 2], 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Summer Programs Binder, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Summer Programs Binder, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Year-long Programs Binder [1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Year-long Programs Binder [2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Office Letter File #209-550, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Office Letter File #1-208, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Office Letter File # 715-894, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Office Letter File # 550-714, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Office Letter File # 336-630 and Index, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Office Letter File # 1-335, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Year-long Program Binder [1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Year-long Program Binder [2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Year-long Program File [1 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Year-long Program File [2 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Office Letter File #493-786, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Office Letter File #104-492, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Office Letter File #1-103, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Office Letter File #787-996, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Office Letter File# 632-844, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Year-long Programs Binder [1 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Year-long Programs Binder [1 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Articulation Agreements for International Programs, 1968-1976; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Folders in this series have been arranged alphabetically by institution.
  This artificial series contains articulation agreements between the University at Albany and international institutions governing study abroad programs.
  - CIDOC Cuernavaca Program Agreement, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Israeli Program Memorandum of Understanding, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nice Program Agreement, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Technical University Berlin Research Agreement, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - University of Guadalajara Agreement of Cooperation, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Website for the Center for International Education and Global Strategy, 2008 July 23 - 2017 May 17; 1; 28 captures
  URL
  http://www.albany.edu/international/
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is not a seed within an Archive-it collection, but capures of this page are found within:
  collection: University at Albany, SUNY Website
  created_date: 2012-09-17T13:15:00Z
  created_by: bkeough
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:38:05Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - University at Albany - Office of International Education, 2008 July 23
    Meta tag for description: University at Albany press releases.
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - University at Albany - Office of International Education, 2008 September 7
  - not present, 2012 July 2
  - not present, 2012 July 2
  - University at Albany - Office of International Education, 2013 May 8
    This item had no crawl rules.
    The CDX index for this capture did not contain crawl information.
  - WARC file for University at Albany - Office of International Education, 2013 May 8
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.